<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<blog>
    <post>
        <date>April 25, 2023</date>
        <author>By Glenn Rowley</author>
        <title>Halsey Hypes Up Suga’s Debut Solo Album ‘D-DAY’: ‘Lessss Goooooo’</title>
        <summary>
            <image_path>
                https://www.billboard.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/halsey-bts-billboard-music-awards-2019-billboard-1548.jpg</image_path>
            <text>The pop singer memorably teamed up with Suga and his BTS bandmates for 2019's "Boy
                With Luv."</text>
        </summary>
        <body>The song is a popular choice from Suga’s first full album under his Agust D moniker —
            in fact, it hit the top spot on the Hot Trending Songs chart earlier this month by
            dethroning Tyler, the Creator’s two-week reign with Call Me If You Get Lost: The Estate
            Sale deluxe lead-off “Dogtooth.” In the very same tally dated April 22, Suga commanded
            the No. 3 slot with “AMYGDALA,” as well as three more spots lower down the chart after
            the reveal of the album’s 10-song track list.

            Meanwhile, Halsey has been both a longtime pal and ardent fan of Suga and the rest of
            his BTS bandmates. Back in 2019, she became one of the first American pop stars to
            collaborate with the K-pop boy band, being featured on their Map of the Soul: Persona
            single “Boy With Luv.”</body>
    </post>
    <post>
        <date>April 25, 2023</date>
        <author>By Keith Caulfield</author>
        <title>Metallica, Waterparks, Yung Bleu and Prof Bow in Top 10 on Album Sales Chart</title>
        <summary>
            <image_path>
                https://www.billboard.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Metallica-press-credit-Tim-Saccenti-2022-billboard-1548.jpg</image_path>
            <text>Metallica's "72 Seasons" opens at No. 1 with the biggest sales week for a rock set
                in over three-and-a-half years.</text>
        </summary>
        <body>Billboard’s Top Album Sales chart ranks the top-selling albums of the week based only
            on traditional album sales. The chart’s history dates back to May 25, 1991, the first
            week Billboard began tabulating charts with electronically monitored piece count
            information from SoundScan, now Luminate. Pure album sales were the sole measurement
            utilized by the Billboard 200 albums chart through the list dated Dec. 6, 2014, after
            which that chart switched to a methodology that blends album sales with track equivalent
            album units and streaming equivalent album units. For all chart news, follow @billboard
            and @billboardcharts on both Twitter and Instagram.

            72 Seasons bows with the biggest sales week for any rock or hard rock album since Fear
            Inoculum’s debut with 248,000 sold (No. 1, chart dated Sept. 14, 2019).

            Of 72 Seasons’ 134,000 sold, physical sales comprise 106,500 (59,000 on CD, 42,500 on
            vinyl and 5,000 on cassette) and digital download sales comprise nearly 27,500. The
            vinyl sales sum marks Metallica’s largest sales week for an album on the format since
            Luminate began tracking sales in 1991.

            Waterparks collects its highest-charting set and best sales week yet as Intellectual
            Property debuts at No. 2 with 16,000 copies sold. It’s the third top 10 for the rock
            act. Melanie Martinez’s former No. 1 Portals falls 2-3 with 13,000 sold (down 33%),
            Taylor Swift’s chart-topping Midnights climbs 5-4 with nearly 13,000 (down 6%) and
            Morgan Wallen’s former leader One Thing at a Time vaults 15-5 with 12,000 (up 102%)
            after a new vinyl edition of the album was released</body>
    </post>
    <post>
        <date>April 24, 2023</date>
        <author>By Jessica Nicholson</author>
        <title>Jelly Roll’s Wife Bunnie XO Defends Morgan Wallen Amid Canceled Concert Backlash</title>
        <summary>
            <image_path>
                https://www.billboard.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Bunnie-Xo-and-Jelly-Roll-2023-cmt-billboard-1548.jpg</image_path>
            <text>I have seen what goes on behind the scenes and it's not easy," she explained on
                Instagram. "Those decisions are never easy.</text>
        </summary>
        <body>She shed light on the effort that artists (including her husband Jelly Roll) put in to
            get onstage and perform for fans, saying, “I have seen my husband getting literally,
            like, two or three breathing treatments because he has bronchitis so bad, and an IV,
            getting a shot of Toradol, taking steroids like the steroid pack that the doctor gives
            you, I mean, like doing all of that just so he makes it onstage, because he knows that
            if he doesn’t make it onstage because, one, the backlash he’ll get, and two, he never
            wants to upset the fans.”

            She added, “When an artist has to make a decision to cancel a show, especially when you
            get to arenas like that, it’s one of the hardest decisions they have ever made. It’s not
            them sitting in the back and saying, like, ‘Oh, you know, I don’t want to show up to
            work today.’ There are so many factors that go into that. Not only that, but they lose
            out on money. They have to pay the venues back. I understand, people have to travel
            thousands of miles to see their favorite artist. I understand that parents have had to
            get babysitters and time off work and this is their one night out that they are really
            looking forward to, but you also have to understand that health is the most important
            thing. If somebody’s sick, they cannot go out there and give their all. If he really
            lost his voice and he went out there onstage and he was singing, [and giving] the worst
            version of himself that he could, not only would you guys be mad at him still — you all
            would be making videos about that, like, ‘Look at Morgan Wallen’s worst performance
            ever’ — and trying to get views from it. An artist is damned if they do, damned if they
            don’t.”</body>
    </post>
</blog> 